<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="title_create_account">Creating a new account</string>
	<string name="title_join_event">Joining an existing event</string>
	<string name="title_create_event">Creating your own event</string>
	<string name="title_edit_account">Edit account settings</string>
	<string name="title_adding_filters">Addings filters to lists</string>
	
	<string name="help_general">Click on the buttons below for help for those subjects</string>
	<string name="help_create_account">To create an account click the register button on the top of the screen. Fill in your name, email address and
	     a password that you want to use for your new account. You can use any email address but if you use a Thales address you will be able to create
	     you own events. Accounts with other mail addresses wil only be able to join existing events.\n\nIf you\'re done filling in your details, press OK
	     and you will be logged in automaticlly</string>
	<string name="help_join_event">If you want to join an event, click on it first. This will show 3 buttons:\n - More Details: Will show you more information
	    on the event like: a description, what time the event will be, the location of the event and the min and max amount of participants\n
	     - People Currently Signed Up: Will show a list of the people who will participate in the event, if there are already people signed up\n
	      - Sign Up: Pressings this will sign you up for an event.</string>
	<string name="help_create_event">To create an event you must have a Thales account. You will automaticlly have a Thales account if you used your
	    thales email address when creating your account\n\nIf you press the plus symbool on the top of the screen you will go to the event creation screen
	    Simply fill in all the fields and press the OK button on the top of the screen. You event will now show up in the Events tab</string>
	<string name="help_edit_account">If you want to edit some information of your account, go to the navigation drawer by clicking on the right of the 
	    top bar of by swiping to the right from the left side of your screen. Click on Profile.\n\nHere you can change your name and password by clicking
	    the pen on the right and you can set a profile picture by clicking on the current profile picture</string>
	<string name="help_adding_filters">If you want to filter events, locations or people on certain things, click the magnifying glass on the top of the
	    screen. On this screen you can add or remove filters. If for example you add the filter name \"contains abc\" and go back to the list, you will only
	    find events, locations or people where the name contains abc.\n\nYou can add as many filters as you want, the current filtes will be shown below the
	    create button. You can remove filters by clicking the red x to the right of it</string>
    
</resources>
